In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
What is this?
Why?
Why are we here?
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
Time of Eternity
The symbol that has
been branded on to your skin...
...marks you as sacrificial offerings.
The lives of those
who have been branded now...
...belong to us as offerings.
Every last drop of your blood...
...until your dying gasps...
...is food for the life of our
beloved unborn child of darkness.
Wait!
Hang on, Griffith!
I'll get you out of there soon!
It's no use!
Human strength is utterly
useless in this situation.
Your efforts are futile in this matter.
All is dictated by his own will.
Shut up!
You must have heard what we said...
He's the one who has the final word.
I said...
Shut up!
That's not possible!
Was it you...
Was it you who wanted this?
Sacrifice, sacrifice, sacrifice...
Pippin!
Run!
Go!
Run! Run away!
You must survive!
What are you saying?
What are you doing?
Let go! Pippin is...
Pippin!
We can't leave him there to die!
Stop it!
You are our leader now!
You must survive!
If our commander's alive,
it's not over for the Band of the Hawk!
Not like this!
I won't let it be over... Not like this!
Commander!
A dream.
This is all a dream!
The Midland army...
The Band of the Hawk...
It was all a dream!
If you think about it,
it was all too good to be true...
That's right!
All a dream!
This is all a dream!
When I open my eyes,
everything will be over!
It'll just be me.
A woman in hell?
This must be a dream.
Damn it.
I'm such a sucker.
Why?
Damn it.
Judeau, to your right!
Judeau!
Are you all right?
Yeah, you saved me.
Judeau...
That's enough...
Turn back!
It's the same wherever we go!
They'll come after us!
We should at least go down together
with our swords in our hands.
Quiet, you'll bite your tongue!
We've got to struggle through it.
We have to keep struggling
right to the bitter end.
I'll be damned if we go back
to face them just to get killed.
No thanks, I don't want that.
Guts wouldn't either.
Judeau!
You fool! Get out of the way!
Why are you...
That's enough.
Stop!
Judeau!
Did I get him?
With my last knife?
Yes, you got him.
He's dead.
Go...
What the hell are you saying?
You just said we have to struggle
and struggle until the very end!
Stand up!
I'm taking you with me,
even if I have to drag you!
All right...
I'll accompany you.
Even if it means I have to crawl...
Yes, you'd better!
I guess I wasn't in my right
mind when I said all that.
Take responsibility for your own words.
I'm afraid I've always been,
you know, all talk.
If you have the strength for excuses...
...use it to walk!
I always thought I was
at least pretty articulate...
...but it looks like I missed my chance...
Those crucial words...
You sure do cry a lot, don't you?
And those are my last words...
Judeau?
The living sacrifice...
Living sacrifice...
The sacrificial woman...
Shall we eat?
Shall we eat now?
But before that...
Before that...
Guts!
That boy really does try hard, doesn't he?
Isn't it ironic?
The more powerful his vitality is...
...and the longer
he draws out this struggle...
...the more precious he will be for the
new life to feed on in the darkness.
Sweet dreams, our newborn Apostle.
Your entire being is built upon Griffith's dream.
When Griffith's dream dies with him...
...you will finally open your eyes...
...and be brought to life
in your own never-ending dream.
Where...
Where am I?
I feel my body...
...sinking...
...deep...
Their deaths pierce through me.
The men I killed...
Because of my desires...
How strange...
I don't feel a thing...
I'm just sinking...
What's this?
The last tear you shed.
When a person suffers so much
that he is almost torn in two...
...his heart freezes.
Behelits?
These are just splashes...
Splashes spilling
from one ocean to another.
A droplet of the future...
Summoning you from the other world...
Blood!
Isn't anyone alive?
Judeau!
Pippin!
Corkus!
Casca...
Commander...
Gaston!
You're alive!
Well, I hardly feel like I'm alive anymore.
Where's the rest of the group?
Who else is alive?
I don't know.
I was running like hell trying to get away.
Next thing I knew, I found myself like this.
I don't know
what happened to the rest of them.
Commander.
What do you think this means?
It's as if we're in a bad dream.
Gaston!
Pippin!
You're alive!
You bastards!
It is the birth...
...of our fifth blessed ruler...
Our new demon king...
You are one of us...
Our latest kin to wear the crown of evil.
The Wings of Darkness...
Femto!
Griffith?
Griffith!
Oh, it's beautiful...
How it moves me...
Love, hatred, torment, pleasure...
Life and death...
All at once before our eyes...
This is the beauty of man...
...and evil.
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...
You going?
Don't get yourself killed.